{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Curtain Installation Companies","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40168/":{"taskOID":40168,"originalTaskOID":40168,"setID":478,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":200811,"questionDisplayText":"Materials Provided by Customer","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you plan to provide the drapes or curtains for this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1350,"questionDisplayText":"Rooms for Drapery Installation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"In which rooms do you wish to install draperies? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1003,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bedroom","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3628,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Living room","answerDisplayText":"Living room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2380,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Family room","answerDisplayText":"Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1926,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Dining room","answerDisplayText":"Dining room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":983,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3052,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Home office","answerDisplayText":"Home office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1352,"questionDisplayText":"Selected features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select any drapery features you want.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3621,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Lining","answerDisplayText":"Lining","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3304,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Insulation","answerDisplayText":"Insulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6652,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Valance (scarf, pouf, swag, other)","answerDisplayText":"Valance (scarf, pouf, swag, other)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6352,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Tiebacks","answerDisplayText":"Tiebacks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1857,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Decorative rods","answerDisplayText":"Decorative rods","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5620,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Sheers","answerDisplayText":"Sheers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":200811,"questionDisplayText":"Materials Provided by Customer","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you plan to provide the drapes or curtains for this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1350,"questionDisplayText":"Rooms for Drapery Installation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"In which rooms do you wish to install draperies? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1003,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bedroom","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3628,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Living room","answerDisplayText":"Living room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2380,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Family room","answerDisplayText":"Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1926,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Dining room","answerDisplayText":"Dining room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":983,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3052,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Home office","answerDisplayText":"Home office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1003,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bedroom","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3628,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Living room","answerDisplayText":"Living room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2380,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Family room","answerDisplayText":"Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1926,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Dining room","answerDisplayText":"Dining room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":983,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3052,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Home office","answerDisplayText":"Home office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1352,"questionDisplayText":"Selected features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select any drapery features you want.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3621,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Lining","answerDisplayText":"Lining","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3304,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Insulation","answerDisplayText":"Insulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6652,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Valance (scarf, pouf, swag, other)","answerDisplayText":"Valance (scarf, pouf, swag, other)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6352,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Tiebacks","answerDisplayText":"Tiebacks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1857,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Decorative rods","answerDisplayText":"Decorative rods","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5620,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Sheers","answerDisplayText":"Sheers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3621,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Lining","answerDisplayText":"Lining","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3304,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Insulation","answerDisplayText":"Insulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6652,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Valance (scarf, pouf, swag, other)","answerDisplayText":"Valance (scarf, pouf, swag, other)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6352,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Tiebacks","answerDisplayText":"Tiebacks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1857,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Decorative rods","answerDisplayText":"Decorative rods","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5620,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Sheers","answerDisplayText":"Sheers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40168/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40168,"taskName":"Drapes or Curtains - Install or Replace","taskDescription":"Install or Replace Drapes or Curtains","xmTaskDescriptor":"Curtain Installation Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":275,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Drapes blinds mounted custom drapery","textMessagingName":"Install Drapes","rolloverLongDesc":"Typically handled by decorators or window treatment specialty firms.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes rods \u0026 valances if needed.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace Drapes or Curtains.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Curtain Installation - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install Drapes \u0026 Curtains","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":24,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":4,"bridgeTaskOid":39794,"bridgeTaskText":"Note: If your repair is not very complex or you have a variety of small projects, you might consider ","bridgeTaskLinkText":"requesting a Handyman.","bridgeTaskLinkId":1437,"bridgeTaskActive":"Y","xmName":"Window Coverings or Curtains Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Drapes or Curtains - Install or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Drapes and Curtain Project","urlName":"Drapes-or-Curtains-Install-or-Replace","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Curtain Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Drape \u0026 Curtain Install, Costs","searchKeywords":"drapes, drapery, draperies, curtains, window coverings, window, coverings, window treaments","emcCategoryOid":-12079,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":478,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"isCookielessUser":true}